

CONTACT

Born 1989 in Brazil



Brazil





@thejohnlima github.com/thejohnlima



https://linkedin.com/in/thejohnlim

SKILLS

Obj-C

MVVM

SPM

Agile Methodologies

JOHN LIMA

IOS DEVELOPER

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept of the ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.

EXPERIENCE

tvOS | iOS Developer - FreeCast Inc Since January 2021

Working with Swift for iOS and tvOS apps

iOS Engineer - PagSeguro UOL July 2018 - March 2021

Working with native apps using Swift

iOS Developer - Stormbreaker Studios January 2020 - December 2020

Working in iOS apps using Swift

iOS Developer - BRQ April 2017 - June 2018

Working with native apps using Swift and Objective-C

iOS Developer - Magna Sistemas

February 2016 - April 2017

Working with native apps using Swift

iOS Developer - Urban Summer

March 2015 - February 2016

Working with native and hybrid apps

EDUCATION

System Analysis and Development